quiz=[{number:"question1",id:"1",question:"Which type of JavaScript language is ___",answer:"Object-Based",
options:[object-Oriented,object-Based,Assembly-language,High-level]},

{number:"question2",id:"2",question:" In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",answer:"block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",options:"[Conditional block,block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement,both conditional block and a single statement,block that contains a single statement]"},

{number:"question3",id:"3",question:"The function and  var are known as:",answer:"Declaration statements",options:"[Keywords,Data types,Declaration statements,Prototypes]"},

{number:"question4",id:"4",question:"Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",answer:"Mutable variable",options:"[Mutable variable,Dynamic variable,Volatile variable,Immutable variable]"},

{number:"question5",id:"5",question:"In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",answer:"Division by zero",options:"[Syntax error,Missing of semicolons,Division by zero,Missing of Bracket]"},

{number:"question6",id:"6",question:"Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",answer:"valueOf()",options:"[toString(),valueOf(),toLocaleString(),toPrecision()]"},

{number:"question7",id:"7",question:" In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression:",answer:"Function literal",options:"[Function prototype,,Function_literal, Function_calling,Function_declaration]"},

{number:"question8",id:"8",question:"Which one of the following operator is used to check weather a specific property exists or not:",answer:"in",options:"[Exists,exist,within,in]"},

{number:"question9",id:"9",question:"Which one of the following is an ternary operator:",answer:"?",options:"[?,:,-,+]"},

 
{number:"question10",id:"10",question:"In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL , the typeof returned by the unary operator is___.",answer:"object",options:"[undefined,string,boolean,object]"}]